# Shayan Yousefian

Web Developer

Address: St. Catharines, ON



T +1 647 863 1891 info@shayanys.com

### **About Me**



Software developer with more than 5 years of experience in web-based startups. Fast learner, with conceptual thinking. Good taste in art and design, piano player and photography enthusiast. My passion is to be a game developer and an entrepreneur. In general, I love creating new things, that's why I became a software developer.

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### Back End PHP Developer, HostPapa

Ontario, Canada — Mar 2018 - present

Django (Python), REST APIs, Laravel (PHP), Wordpress (Plug-in and Theme development and maintenance)

#### Accomplishments:

- Creating an inovative and successful advertisement platform named, Yektanet.com.
- High-Performance web-service and database design.

# Senior Full Stack Developer, Yektanet

Tehran, Iran — Mar 2016 - July 2018



Django (Python), REST APIs, Laravel (PHP), Wordpress (Plug-in and Theme development and maintenance)

#### Accomplishments:

- Creating an inovative and successful advertisement platform named, Yektanet.com.
- High-Performance web-service and database design.

# Back End PHP Developer, Bamilo

Tehran, Iran — Aug 2015 - Mar 2016

Laravel (PHP), Live transactions for e-mail marketing and data-processing migrations for business, Telegram Bot for marketing.

#### Accomplishments:

- Tight deadlines, International workplace.
- Creating inter-connection between different platforms using crawling and queries.

#### Junior Full Stack Developer, Pordo

Tehran, Iran — Feb 2013- Aug 2015

Codeigniter (PHP), Multi-purpose CMS development and static page designs.

#### Accomplishments:

- Creating fully-customized CMS.
- Front-End development for dozens of websites.

#### **SKILLS**



COLLABORATIVE FAST LEARNER DRIVEN TO DELIVER CREATIVE
DISCRETE AND ETHICAL
MULTI TASKING

# **EDUCATION**

#### **Computer Science – Post-Graduate**

Brock University, Ontario, Canada — 2017-2018 (expected, end of year)

Currently working on "Autogenerating quests for Role-Playing-Games" as my Master Project under the supervision of professor Michael Winter.



#### **Computer Engineering – Under-Graduate**

Shahid Beheshti, Tehran, Iran — 2012-2017

Dynamic server optimizer application as Bachelor's Project, GPA: 3.67 (major courses).

#### Physics and Mathematics – High School

Allameh-Helli, Tehran, Iran — 2008-2012

In this special school for talented students, I completed all the credits and got A<sup>+</sup> grade overall.

# **LANGUAGES**

English: fluent (TOEFL: 100) Persian: native language

#### **HONORS - AWARDS**



Admitted to State University (Shahid Beheshti, Tehran)

National Universities Entrance Exam (Concours) —2012

Ranked 1500 from 1.66 millions contestants.